Step out into the sun
Skies above they radiate me
Lift up, carry the love
Do you know?
That I've been out of my mind
This slow life I'm waiting for you
To swing me all of your line
Do you know?
Since I've been walking solo
Dreaming you were back home
Hi-fi getting down low
Hide until tomorrow
Come back into the good life
Lose these hazy love lies
I've been chasing my mind
Lonely in the cold nights
'Cause I'm kicking up stones without you
Can't pick up the phone without you
I'm a little bit lost without you
Without you
And I'm digging down holes without you
Can't be on my own without you
I'm a little bit lost without you
Without you
Step out into the dark
Where were you when I was trying
To lift up, carry the love?
Do you know?
That I've been closing my eyes
Love me slow, hallucinating
Swinging me all of your light
Do you know?
Since I've been walking solo
Dreaming you were back home
Hi-fi find getting down low
Hide until tomorrow
Come back into the good life
Lose these hazy love lies
I've been chasing my mind
Lonely in the cold nights
'Cause I'm kicking up stones without you
Can't pick up the phone without you
I'm a little bit lost without you
Without you
And I'm digging down holes without you
Can't be on my own without you
I'm a little bit lost without you
Without you, oh
Hold me close when it's over
Life goes slow loving sober
Feel my bones getting older
Sadness grows when you're cold
'Cause I am one step heavy and two steps high
Hold it steady with you by my side
One step heavy and two steps high
Two steps high
'Cause I'm kicking up stones without you
Can't pick up the phone without you
I'm a little bit lost without you
And I'm digging down holes without you
Can't be on my own without you
I'm a little bit lost without you
Without you
And I'm digging down holes without you
Can't be on my own without you
I'm a little bit lost without you
Without you